Goodspeed Musicals Scherer Library of Musical Theatre Priority Archive
Goodspeed Musicals
- Inventory
  - Look Before You Leap; Or, Wooings & Weddings, 1846; Theatre Royal Hay-Market Nov. 1846; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 20.25 x 9.75; Barcode: 35111000005334 (Box 4*)
  - Macbeth, undated; 1836, performance concluded with "Fra-Diavolo!"; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 9 x 13; Barcode: 35111000005342 (Box 4*)
  - Julius Caesar & Masaniello, undated; Theatre Broadside, Theatre Royal Drury-Lane; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 8.25 x 14; Barcode: 35111000005359 (Box 4*)
  - Guy Mannering, 1855; Theatre Royal Hay-Market, Nov. 1855; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 9.5 x 20.5; Barcode: 35111000005375 (Box 4*)
  - Victims!, 1857; Theatre Royal Hay-Market, Jul.-Aug. 1857; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 20 x 9.75; Barcode: 35111000005771 (Box 4*)
  - Wife's Secret, 1864; Wallack's, Dec. 1864; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 12 x 5.5; Barcode: 35111000005870 (Box 4*)
  - Woman's Heart, undated; Theatre Royal Hay-Market March 1852; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 22.75 x 12; Barcode: 35111000005888 (Box 4*)
  - Romeo & Juliet, undated; Theatre Royal Covent Garden, performance concluded with "Harlequin & Cinderella"; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 12.5 x 8.5; Barcode: 35111000005953 (Box 4*)
  - Werner Or, The Inheritance, undated; Theatre Royal Drury-Lane, 1830, performance concluded with "Masaniello"; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 8.75 x 13.75; Barcode: 35111000005961 (Box 4*)
  - Second Love!, undated; Theatre Royal Hay-Market, Sept. 1856; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 20.5 x 10; Barcode: 35111000005979 (Box 4*)
  - King Richard the Third, 1824; Theatre Royal Drury-Lane, 1824, performance concluded with "Harlequin and the Flying Chest"; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 1; Dimensions: 14.25 x 9.5; Barcode: 35111000005367 (Box 4*)
  - 13- A New Musical Comedy, undated; 2008 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GAC Playbill; Page count: 34; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000012 (Box 5*)
  - All Shook Up, undated; 2004 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GAC Playbill; Page count: 24; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000020 (Box 5*)
  - By Jeeves, undated; 1996 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GAC Playbill; Page count: 28; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000038 (Box 5*)
  - Swinging On A Star, undated; 1995 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 68; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000046 (Box 5*)
  - Gentleman Prefer Blondes, undated; 1994 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 68; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000053 (Box 5*)
  - The Most Happy Fella, undated; 1991 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 65; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000061 (Box 5*)
  - Take Me Along, undated; 1984 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 74; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000087 (Box 5*)
  - Man of La Mancha, undated; 2000 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 76; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000095 (Box 5*)
  - Harrington 'N Hart, undated; 1984 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GAC Playbill; Page count: 24; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000103 (Box 5*)
  - Little Johnny Jones, undated; 1978 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 56; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000111 (Box 5*)
  - Whoopee, undated; 1978 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 52; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000129 (Box 5*)
  - Going Up, 1976; 1976 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 40; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000137 (Box 5*)
  - Annie, 1976; 1976 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 44; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000145 (Box 5*)
  - Very Good Eddie, 1975; 1975 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 38; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000000152 (Box 5*)
  - Vagabond King, undated; Title Page and Credits only; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 6 X 14; Barcode: 35111000000160 (Box 5*)
  - Connecticut Yankee, undated; Title Page and Credits only; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 6.25 X 9; Barcode: 35111000000178 (Box 5*)
  - Chu Chin Chow, undated; Washington, D.C.; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 9 X 11; Barcode: 35111000000194 (Box 5*)
  - Around the World, undated; New York Hippodrome; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 30; Dimensions: 4.25 X 9; Barcode: 35111000000269 (Box 5*)
  - Man Who Owns Broadway, undated; Nixon Theatre - Pittsburgh; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 37; Dimensions: 8 X 9.5; Barcode: 35111000000293 (Box 5*)
  - Midnight Sons, undated; Brooklyn; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 17; Dimensions: 8 X 9.5; Barcode: 35111000000301 (Box 5*)
  - Tillie's Nightmare, undated; Brooklyn; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 29; Dimensions: 7.5 X 9.5; Barcode: 35111000000319 (Box 5*)
  - Jamaica, undated; Boston; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 6 X 9.5; Barcode: 35111000000335 (Box 5*)
  - Passing Show of 1919, undated; Hartford Parsons Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 14; Dimensions: 5.5 X 9; Barcode: 35111000000434 (Box 5*)
  - Up and Down Broadway, undated; The Alvin Theatre - Pittsburgh; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 28; Dimensions: 6 x 9; Barcode: 35111000000558 (Box 5*)
  - OH, Kay!, undated; Royal Alexandra; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 6; Dimensions: 5.75 x 11; Barcode: 35111000000574 (Box 5*)
  - Come As You Are, undated; Program; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 6; Dimensions: 5.25 X 7; Barcode: 35111000000582 (Box 5*)
  - Take Me Along, undated; Boston before New York - Shubert Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 6 X 9.5; Barcode: 35111000000590 (Box 5*)
  - A Night In Paris, undated; featured stars: Ray Bolger, Norma Terris; Items: 1; Format: program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 11 x 4.75; Barcode: 35111000000608 (Box 5*)
  - Goldilocks, undated; Shubert Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 6 X 9; Barcode: 35111000000749 (Box 5*)
  - Grab Bag, undated; Garrick Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 4.25 X 6; Barcode: 35111000000756 (Box 5*)
  - The City Suite, undated; Park Royal Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 5.5 X 8.5; Barcode: 35111000000764 (Box 5*)
  - Under Many Flags, undated; New York Hippodrome; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 28; Dimensions: 4.25 X 9; Barcode: 35111000000772 (Box 5*)
  - Something's Afoot, undated; 1973 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 36; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000001002 (Box 5*)
  - Man of La Mancha, 1965; 1965 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 24; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000001010 (Box 5*)
  - The New Moon, undated; Imperial Theatre, March 1929; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 60; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000001200 (Box 5*)
  - The Little Show, undated; Music Box Theatre, June 1929; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 36; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000001218 (Box 5*)
  - Liliom, undated; Fulton Theatre Dec. 1921; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 27; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000001341 (Box 5*)
  - Ziegfeld Midnight Frolic, undated; Ziegfeld Roof shows created to try out material for the main Ziegfeld Follies. December 1921; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 19; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000001358 (Box 5*)
  - Kelly, 1965; The legendary failure, then the most expensive failure in Broadway history. 1965; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 60; Dimensions: 9 x 6; Barcode: 35111000001366 (Box 5*)
  - Guys and Dolls, undated; Sam Levene, Vivian Blaine, Robert Alda; Items: 1; Format: Tryout program; Page count: 1 & 11; Dimensions: 8.5 x 13; Barcode: 35111000001374 (Box 5*)
  - The Frogs, undated; Yale Repertory (Stephen Sondheim, Burt Shevelove); Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 9; Dimensions: 12.5 x 5.5; Barcode: 35111000001382 (Box 5*)
  - Music Box Revue, undated; The Music Box; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 51; Dimensions: 7.5 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000001390 (Box 5*)
  - The Belle of Bridgeport, undated; Bijou Theatre, 19th Century; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 16; Dimensions: 8 x 10; Barcode: 35111000001416 (Box 5*)
  - The Belle of New York, undated; Casino Theatre & Roof Garden, 19th Century; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 10; Dimensions: 8 x 10; Barcode: 35111000001424 (Box 5*)
  - The Telephone Girl, undated; Casino Theatre & Roof Garden, 19th Century; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 16; Dimensions: 8 x 10; Barcode: 35111000001432 (Box 5*)
  - A Chinese Honeymoon, undated; Casino Theatre & Roof Garden, 19th Century; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 36; Dimensions: 8 x 10; Barcode: 35111000001440 (Box 5*)
  - The Highwayman, undated; Broadway Theatre, 19th Century; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 16; Dimensions: 8 x 10; Barcode: 35111000001457 (Box 5*)
  - She's My Baby, 1928; Globe Theatre, 1928; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 28; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5; Barcode: 35111000001473 (Box 5*)
  - The Faggot, undated; Early gay-themed musical; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 9 x 5.75; Barcode: 35111000001481 (Box 5*)
  - Up From Paradise, undated; Only musical by Arthur Miller; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 9; Dimensions: 8.5 x 5.5; Barcode: 35111000001499 (Box 5*)
  - Pousse-Café, undated; Only Broadway musical written by Duke Ellington.; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 3(4); Dimensions: 9 x 6; Barcode: 35111000001507 (Box 5*)
  - Follies of 1910, undated; Photograph included; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 35; Dimensions: 9.75 x 7.75; Barcode: 35111000001515 (Box 5*)
  - Plays and Players, undated; Includes playbills from Sergant Brue, You Never Can Tell, Candida, and Miss Dolly Dollar. 1905; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 24; Dimensions: 8.25 x 10.125; Barcode: 35111000001531 (Box 5*)
  - Ziegfeld Follies, undated; Thirteenth Edition starring Eddie Cantor and Bert Williams, the first black entertainer billed as a star on Broadway Oct.1919; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 47; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000001549 (Box 5*)
  - Anyone Can Whistle, undated; New Musical with Angela Landsbury; Items: 1; Format: Broadside; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 9 x 6; Barcode: 35111000004519 (Box 5*)
  - Shenandoah, undated; 1974 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GOH Playbill; Page count: 36; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000001036 (Box 6*)
  - Oh, Boy!, undated; The Casino; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 25; Dimensions: 6 X 9; Barcode: 35111000001119 (Box 6*)
  - Rumple, undated; Boston; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 5.25 X 8.75; Barcode: 35111000001127 (Box 6*)
  - Rollicking Girl, undated; Herald Square Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 32; Dimensions: 6 X 9; Barcode: 35111000001135 (Box 6*)
  - Rhyth-Mania, undated; The Famous Cotton Club; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 2; Dimensions: 9.75 x 13; Barcode: 35111000001143 (Box 6*)
  - Going Up, undated; John Golden Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 5.75 X 9; Barcode: 35111000001168 (Box 6*)
  - Seven Come Eleven, undated; Example of the intimate musical revue, long fold-out format; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 8; Dimensions: 7.25 x 5.5; Barcode: 35111000001176 (Box 6*)
  - The Story Of My Life, undated; 2008 at Goodspeed went to Broadway; Items: 1; Format: GAC Playbill; Page count: 42; Dimensions: 5.5X8.5; Barcode: 35111000001192 (Box 6*)
  - The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, undated; One of the first musicals to be work shopped prior to production; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 6; Dimensions: 8.5 x 5.5; Barcode: 35111000001226 (Box 6*)
  - Greenwich Village, U.S.A., undated; New York; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 5.5 X 8.5; Barcode: 35111000001242 (Box 6*)
  - George Gershwin Concert, undated; Springfield, Mass. Auditorium, Jan. 17, 1934, autographed by George Gershwin; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 8.75 x 5.5; Barcode: 35111000001275 (Box 6*)
  - Oklahoma!, undated; Playbill for the St. James Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 40; Dimensions: 9 x 6.75; Barcode: 35111000001283 (Box 6*)
  - This Year of Grace, undated; Selwyn Theatre, February 1929; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 68; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000001309 (Box 6*)
  - Gypsy, undated; Shubert, Ethel Merman production; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 16; Dimensions: 9 x 6; Barcode: 35111000001317 (Box 6*)
  - Earl Carroll Vanities (8th Edition), undated; New Amsterdam theatre, September 1930; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 44; Dimensions: 9.5 x 7; Barcode: 35111000001325 (Box 6*)
  - Of Thee I Sing, undated; Music Box Theatre, May 1932; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 44; Dimensions: 9.5 x 7; Barcode: 35111000001333 (Box 6*)
  - Monte Cristo, Jr., undated; Winter Garden Theatre Oct. 1919; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 39; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000001556 (Box 6*)
  - The Little Cherub, undated; Park Theatre, Boston, 1907; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 24; Dimensions: 5.25 x 7.75; Barcode: 35111000001945 (Box 6*)
  - Pins and Needles, undated; Labor Stage, New York, 1939; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 16; Dimensions: 7 x 10; Barcode: 35111000001952 (Box 6*)
  - A Connecticut Yankee, undated; Parsons Theatre, Hartford; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 26; Dimensions: 5.75 x 8.75; Barcode: 35111000001978 (Box 6*)
  - Strike Me Pink, undated; Majestic Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 38; Dimensions: 7 x 9.5; Barcode: 35111000001994 (Box 6*)
  - Fine and Dandy, undated; Erlanger's Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 52; Dimensions: 7 x 9.5; Barcode: 35111000002000 (Box 6*)
  - Humpty Dumpty, undated; Colonial Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 28; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000002034 (Box 6*)
  - M'lle Modiste, undated; Colonial Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 32; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000002059 (Box 6*)
  - The Grand Mogul, undated; Colonial Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 32; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000002067 (Box 6*)
  - Little Nemo, undated; Colonial Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 24; Dimensions: 7.75 x 5.25; Barcode: 35111000002075 (Box 6*)
  - Hearts of Oak, undated; Arch St. Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 10.5 x 7; Barcode: 35111000002083 (Box 6*)
  - Hearts of Oak, undated; South Broad St. Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 9.5 x 6; Barcode: 35111000002091 (Box 6*)
  - Rip Van Winkle; Or, The Sleep of Twenty Years, undated; Broad St. Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 7.5 x 10; Barcode: 35111000002109 (Box 6*)
  - Music Box Revue, undated; The Music Box, December 1921; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 51; Dimensions: 9.5 x 6; Barcode: 35111000002125 (Box 6*)
  - Music in the Air, undated; Alvin Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 22; Dimensions: 9.5 x 7; Barcode: 35111000002133 (Box 6*)
  - Romeo and Juliet, undated; Fifty-First Street Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 20; Dimensions: 9 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002141 (Box 6*)
  - You Touched Me!, undated; The Booth Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 28; Dimensions: 9 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002158 (Box 6*)
  - Billion Dollar Baby, undated; Monte Proser's Café Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 8; Dimensions: 9 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002166 (Box 6*)
  - Hi Ya, Gentlemen, undated; Colonial Theatre, Boston, 1940; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 6; Dimensions: 8.75 x 5; Barcode: 35111000002174 (Box 6*)
  - Tangerine, undated; Casino Theatre, New York, NY; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 35; Dimensions: 9.5 x 6; Barcode: 35111000002182 (Box 6*)
  - South Pacific, undated; Majestic Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 48; Dimensions: 9 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002208 (Box 6*)
  - Maggie, undated; Forrest Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 12; Dimensions: 9 x 6; Barcode: 35111000002216 (Box 6*)
  - Rip Van Winkle; Or, The Sleep of Twenty Years, undated; Broad Street Theatre, Philadelphia, April 1879; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 4; Dimensions: 10.75 x 7.5; Barcode: 35111000002109 (Box 6*)
  - Romeo and Juliet, undated; Fifty-First Street Theatre; Items: 1; Format: Program; Page count: 20; Dimensions: 9 x 6.5; Barcode: 35111000002141 (Box 6*)
  - Character Sketches of Romance Fiction & Drama, undated; By: Rev E Cobham Brewer, LLD, pub: Selmas Hess (NY) 1896; Items: 1; Format: Book; Page count: 393; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000004733 (Box 7*)
  - Federal Theatre Project, undated; WPA project July 1936 Highlight of the 1st production conference of the NYC unitof the Federal theatre; Items: 1; Format: Administrative; Page count: 29; Dimensions: 8.5 x 11; Barcode: 35111000000947 (Box 8*)
  - 50th Anniversary Souvenir Book, undated; 50 year history of Goodspeed Musicals; Items: 1; Format: Glossy Brochure; Page count: 52; Dimensions: 9X13; Barcode: 35111000001077 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume One, Number One (September 1981); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 5; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000006191 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume One, Number Two (January 1982); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 8; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000006258 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume One, Number Three (April 1982); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 8; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000006266 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume One, Number Four (June 1982); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 10; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000006274 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Two, Number One (September 1982); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 12; Dimensions: 8.5 X 11; Barcode: 35111000006282 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Three, Number One (October 1983); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 30; Dimensions: 7 X 8.5; Barcode: 35111000006324 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Three, Number Two (February 1984); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 32; Dimensions: 7 X 8.5; Barcode: 35111000006332 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Three, Number Three (June 1984); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 36; Dimensions: 7 X 8.5; Barcode: 35111000006340 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Three, Number Four (October 1984); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 40; Dimensions: 7 X 8.5; Barcode: 35111000006357 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Four, Number One (February 1985); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 56; Dimensions: 7 X 8.5; Barcode: 35111000006365 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Four, Number Two (June 1985); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 52; Dimensions: 7 X 8.5; Barcode: 35111000006373 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Four, Number Three (October 1985); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 60; Dimensions: 7 X 8.5; Barcode: 35111000006381 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Six, Number One (Spring 1988); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006399 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Nine, Number Two (Summer 1993); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006530 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Six, Number Three (Winter 1988/89); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006597 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Fourteen, Number Two (Summer 1998); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 73; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006621 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Fourteen, Number Three (Fall 1998); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006761 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Seventeen, Number Two (Summer 2001); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006787 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Seventeen, Number Three (Fall 2001); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006795 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Fourteen, Number Four (Winter 1998/99); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 76; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006852 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Fifteen, Number One (Spring 1999); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 84; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006860 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Seventeen, Number Four (Winter 2001/02); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000007066 (Box 8*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Seven, Number Three (Fall 1991); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006415 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Six, Number Four (Summer 1989); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006431 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Seven, Number One (Spring 1991); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 96; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006456 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Seven, Number Two (Summer 1991); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006563 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Seven, Number Four (Winter 1991/92); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 80; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006605 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Twelve, Number Four (Winter 1996/97); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 68; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006613 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Seventeen, Number One (Spring 2001); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 84; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006779 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Fourteen, Number One (Spring 1998); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 76; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006811 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Thirteen, Number Two (Summer 1997); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006878 (Box 9*)
  - Show Music, undated; Volume Thirteen, Number One (Spring 1997); Items: 1; Format: Goodspeed Archival Magazine; Page count: 72; Dimensions: 8 X 10.5; Barcode: 35111000006886 (Box 9*)